nbanews.us 2010-05-19

# Privacy Policy « NBA News, NBA Results, on – NBANews.us

**NBANews.us** has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site:    NBANews.us.

**External Links**  
\- This site contains links to other sites. NBANews.us is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.

**Security**  
\- This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. E-Mail addresses are not stored on this webserver.

**Children’s Guidelines**  
\- We care about children and understand that they have special privacy needs. Therefore, we have adopted the following privacy policy regarding children:

\- We will NOT collect, use, or distribute to third parties personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent.

\- We will NOT give the child access to unmonitored chat rooms, email accounts, or other services that would give the child the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable information without prior verifiable parental consent. When verifiable parental consent is not obtained, we will only use the online contact information (such as email) to:

\- Respond directly to the child’s request on a one-time basis and not use that information to re-contact the child for other purposes.

\- Request the name or online contact information of a parent for the purpose of obtaining verifiable parental consent or providing parental notification.

\- Respond more than once directly to a specific request from a child (such as in the case where a child requests a newsletter subscription) and not used to re-contact the child for other purposes. We will use our best efforts to provide parental notification, which will include the nature and intended use as well as an opportunity for the parent to prevent the use of the information and participation in the activity.

\- We will NOT entice the child to divulge more information than is needed to participate in any activity, game, or service.

\- We will provide the parent a description of the specific types of a personally identifiable information collected from their child upon request. We will allow the parent to refuse further use or future online collection of personally identifiable information and provide a way for a parent to obtain any personally identifiable information collected from their child.

\- We will provide notice to children in age appropriate terms of what personally identifiable information is to be collected.

\- We will NOT provide any links to Web sites that are unsuitable for children.

\- We will encourage children to get their parent’s permission before sharing personal information online.

**Contacting the Web Site**  
\- If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact: the owner through (Contact Us) bottom

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, read the following.

* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

**Submit Notice**  
\- By submitting any “Content” (information, forum posts, one-liners, links, feedback, content, etc) to NBANews.us or any NBANews.us staff member; you grant us a nonexclusive worldwide license to link to, reproduce, distribute, adapt, perform, display and sublicense the submitted Content. Further, by submitting Content to NBANews.us or any NBANews.us staff member, you acknowledge that you have the authority to grant us such rights. Please note that you retain ownership of any copyrights of all content you submit. If the submitted Content includes information or source code, which is in any way objectionable or harmful, our staff shall have the right to analyze, summarize, and report on this information as we see fit. Since this is a public website, most of our content was submitted to us by our users (forum posts, submitted one-liners, etc). Please notify us ASAP if you find any content on NBANews harmful and offensive and we’ll be more than happy to remove it, usually within the next 3 business day.
